Farewell, Earth
The ship that is departing is
The Space Battleship
Yamato
It departs now to Iscandar,
at the end of the cosmos,
bearing its fate.
"We will come back, no matter what it takes"
Answer with a smile to the waving people
Going far from the Galaxy towards Iscandar
A faint gleam of hope
The Space Battleship Yamato
Small Magellanic Cloud
Outskirts
<Hit!>
<We've created an opening in the enemy lines.>
<Divide the enemy.>
<The 7th Strike Group is to advance!>
<Drive a wedge through them!>
<Flatten them!>
The Milky Way Galaxy
Cell #1
Earth in Danger
Official Government Material
Record of Our War Against the Aliens
Lunar Inner Planet Fleet Setting Out
Japanese Fleet Setting Sail from Fuji Spaceport
Admiral Juzo Okita
Captain Daigo Shima, Killed in Battle
Episode 11
A World I Once Saw
Believe that
Only the future
Has the answer
No one knows
Memory only strikes at
The heart to find
The truth
Do not forget it…
Many stars lie beyond
The spiral of memory
Sparkling in what looks like
The light of memory